(Penny:)You dog.
(Penny:)Good for you.
- Does that change things?
- No.
- So why'd you ask?
- I'm nosy. See you.
MRS. WOLOWITZ [SHOUTING]:
Howard, get the door!
HOWARD [SHOUTING]: Really? Is that
what you do when someone knocks?
(Howard(voice):)Thank you, I had no idea!
[IN NORMAL TONE] Hey, buddy.
What brings you to my little slice of hell?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Who is it?
- It's Leonard!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You're gonna have to play outside!
(Howard's Mother(voice):)I'm not dressed to receive!
(Howard:)No one cares, Ma!
(Howard:)So, what's up?
(Leonard:)Listen, I need to talk to you
about something.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
(Howard(his phone rings):)Momentito.
Hello?
(Howard(his phone rings):)Oh, Stephanie, thanks for calling me back.
I was worried.